{"name":"core_web_sm","license":"CC BY-SA 3.0","author":"Xiaoquan Kong","url":"https://xiaoquankong.ai","sources":["OntoNotes 5","Common Crawl","Universal Dependencies"],"email":"u1mail2me@gmail.com","description":"Chinese multi-task CNN trained on OntoNotes, with GloVe vectors trained on Common Crawl. Assigns word vectors, context-specific token vectors, POS tags, dependency parse and named entities.","lang":"zh","pipeline":["tagger","parser","ner"],"spacy_version":">=2.2.3","speed":{"nwords":41774,"cpu":26140.0529585716,"gpu":null},"accuracy":{"uas":0.0,"las":0.0,"las_per_type":{"":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0}},"ents_p":45.2635914333,"ents_r":36.4510779436,"ents_f":40.382142201,"ents_per_type":{"LOC":{"p":56.5217391304,"r":16.4556962025,"f":25.4901960784},"PERSON":{"p":38.188976378,"r":45.4332552693,"f":41.4973262032},"GPE":{"p":70.0887198986,"r":85.4714064915,"f":77.0194986072},"CARDINAL":{"p":19.5918367347,"r":11.7359413203,"f":14.6788990826},"QUANTITY":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0},"NORP":{"p":40.0,"r":4.7058823529,"f":8.4210526316},"ORG":{"p":40.562248996,"r":23.8770685579,"f":30.0595238095},"DATE":{"p":31.9444444444,"r":33.611691023,"f":32.7568667345},"WORK_OF_ART":{"p":9.0909090909,"r":2.5,"f":3.9215686275},"EVENT":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0},"FAC":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0},"LAW":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0},"TIME":{"p":51.724137931,"r":15.625,"f":24.0},"ORDINAL":{"p":66.6666666667,"r":11.4285714286,"f":19.512195122},"PERCENT":{"p":9.2592592593,"r":9.8039215686,"f":9.5238095238},"MONEY":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0},"PRODUCT":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0},"LANGUAGE":{"p":0.0,"r":0.0,"f":0.0}},"tags_acc":88.6501766784,"token_acc":82.5776798966,"textcat_score":0.0,"textcats_per_cat":{}},"vectors":{"width":128,"vectors":126960,"keys":126960,"name":"zh_core_wiki_sm.vectors"},"version":"0.1.0","labels":{"tagger":["\"","''","(",")",",",".","...","/",":","ADD","AS","BB","CC","CD","DEC","DEV","DT","EC","FW","HYPH","IN","JJ","LS","MD","NN","NNB","NNP","PFA","PFN","PRD","PRP","RB","SFA","SFN","SFV","UH","VC","VERB","VV","WP","_SP","``"],"parser":["ROOT","acl","acl:relcl","advcl","advmod","amod","appos","aux","aux:pass","case","case:aspect","case:dec","case:pref","cc","ccomp","clf","compound","conj","cop","csubj","dep","det","discourse","dislocated","flat:foreign","flat:name","iobj","mark","mark:advb","mark:relcl","nmod","nmod:tmod","nsubj","nsubj:pass","nummod","obj","obl","obl:patient","parataxis","punct","xcomp"],"ner":["CARDINAL","DATE","EVENT","FAC","GPE","LANGUAGE","LAW","LOC","MONEY","MachineLearning","MicrosoftAzure","NORP","ORDINAL","ORG","PERCENT","PERSON","PRODUCT","QUANTITY","TIME","WORK_OF_ART"]},"factories":{"tagger":"tagger","parser":"parser","ner":"ner"}}